You can turn these clouds blue, can't you?
I wouldn't do that.
If I had done it backwards with a goof, it would have been a mess.
I'll pretend I took this picture with a blue plate.
HANNARIDOS! Kyoto dos!
So, my photo book shoot has started, but
It's hot, very hot.
First of all, it's an indoor shoot, so
I will do my best!
Hannari, I'll do my best!
Are you filming?
We're filming.
If you let me hear this voice...
I'll walk with you.
Have you ever been to Kyoto on vacation?
You get off in Kyoto.
A cafe that looks like almonds.
I see.
Wow!
I'm only on my first or second dress right now, but it's amazing to think how many more 10's I have.
It's amazing taking pictures.
It's amazing to take pictures.
Okay, let's go.
Ready, set, go.
Oh, he's cute.
Let's do this.
That's what I said.
Ending song
Tomorrow that won't be the night sky My heart's voice won't echo
What if I pull the atmosphere with a smile like this
I wonder what will come out.
It's entertainment, so it's a big fortune
Number 5
This one.
Super lucky!
But isn't it good?
It's good!
I'll do my best! With this in my heart!
May good things happen to you!
I'm not too anxious.
I'll be with you all from now on.
I will be your friend from now on!
Thank you very much!
I'm going to have fun!
Is it possible to fall?
Whispering mob channel I'll let you find your love easily
Will you notice my love hidden in the noise
I'll see you again this time, be well and don't forget me
It's the second day!
Didn't we start with yukatas today?
No, we didn't.
We started with different clothes.
Today we're going to walk around the city, go to the beach, and go to the beach.
It's going to be another fun day!
The stairs are amazing!
I'll do my best!
Cute, cute, cute!
Push up, push up, push up!
A souvenir with a round pattern
Let's start summer with this
My thoughts flew to the sky
Bouncing, bouncing, bouncing
I don't want to be left behind
They seem to be swimming through the seasons
Well, here I am in Minami-Senju
There are a lot of difficult feelings
I got a lot of good machines and brought them to Tokyo
I want to make Tokyo happy
I'll do my best!
ana
Good.
car
Yoshigami
I wonder how this shot will turn out if there is no sunset. It's very cloudy now.
ana
It will be hard to hold
Best day of the season
Towards the big one.
Take it easy, take care of yourself.
Be there for me
That's all for this video. Thank you for watching.
How was it?
It was good again, and the sun came out a little bit.
I think we made a good movie.
Was it really cold?
It was lukewarm.
So it was surprisingly fun. I wish I could have gone in a little more.
Please subscribe to our channel!
The sun came out safely, too.
I took a lot of pictures today!
So, day 3 continues!
Good morning!
It's the morning of the third day!
It was supposed to rain in Kyoto yesterday and today.
But it looks like it's going to be sunny
It looks like we'll have a nice view today.
I have seen this
I have seen this.I have seen this before.
I am going to do my fortune now.
This is the most ?
3,000 yen
Please come
I'm coming. Ready.
Ta-da!
Chukichi again.
Maybe I'm definitely lucky in the middle!
In Kyoto, I only got a "Chukichi".
But it looks good, so I'll read it slowly
Bye bye!
Are you going to that place?
It looks like a ski resort! I'm looking forward to it.
I'm used to ropeways, so I'll go to a ski resort or something.
I'm going.
It's so cute!
Rice cooked with salmon roe?
Rice cooked with egg.
Say "rice cooked with salmon roe".
Really.
It really is.
May I?
Yes, it's good.
Okay.
How much!
How much do you think it's worth?
Here it comes!
Yes!
Can you open it?
Oh, my God!
We did it! We got salmon roe on rice!
Next time
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Isn't it like round eyes?
I'm so impressed!
I got to see this with my own eyes.
I'm already making it look like life.
It's a little hard to describe.
Real eyes.
Flesh eyes.
I'm relieved to calm your dirty intities
I'll sing the flower castle, too, so I feel like I've touched it
I liked the controller.
Not even close.
Safe
Oh, obsession
You're on the right track.
Ow!
Can you cut that out for me?
I'm used to being on the ropes.
I'm used to skiing and stuff.
Oh, it's official, if you keep smoking
Samplance to step on the stone
Give him a run and laugh when he falls
In the middle of the meadow
I'm feeling the hard life.
The great outdoors is in Fland
Ta-da!
In the food
In every fiber of my being
Gratitude and courtesy as we get to know each other
Let's sing all the way through
Prayerful ending live
Come on, smile for me
Thank you for watching subtitles
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
We will miss you so much that we will release a second one soon, so please buy it everyone! Please buy it!
Handalin!
You can see it here now.
Cute!
Adorable!
I can still hear it through my earbuds.
This sound is the hustle and bustle of summer
Every time I look for something I like
I can't see it in the reflection
I can reach out and touch it
Communicating with each other
Even through the earphones in my ears
The end
We're done.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to say that the New Year went well.
We had the games for four days.
I think it was a different experience from Kyoto.
It was a lot of fun.
Please buy lots of photos!
Bye bye!
It's not the time for ropeways, it's up to you.
I'm used to ropeways.